SYAHRUN FATHAN HIDAYAH

Phone: +62-812-4442-3801 | Email: syahrulmei002@gmail.com

LinkdIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/syahrun-fathan-hidayah/ | Github: https://github.com/SyahrunFathan

Address: Jl. Lekatu Tatanga District, Palu City

ABOUT ME

My name is Syahrun Fathan Hidayah, I am a student majoring in informatics engineering and have graduated from Tadulako University. When I was a student, I had good soft skills, ranging from public speaking, public relations, to leadership skills that were honed from my experience in joining various organizations. This is one of the reasons for my interest in the world of technology and makes me very enthusiastic about pursuing a career in technology and information business.

EDUCATION

Tadulako University Palu City 2020 - 2024S1 Teknik Informatika | GPA 3.72/4.00

I once participated in a student exchange at the Bandung National Institute of

- Technology. • I has participated in a student organization, namely the Informatics Engineering
- Student Association.

I once joined a student organization, namely the student press organization

MA Alkhairaat Pusat Palu **Palu City** High School | IPS 2017 - 2020

- I once participated in scouting activities
- I have participated in art activities
- I once served as the scout leader

WORK EXPERIENCE

BPBD Provinsi Sulawesi Tengah Palu City Software Engineer Agu 2023 - Des 2023

I am responsible for building a rapid assessment application for the PUSDALOPS team.

MY PROJECT

Face Recognition Attendance Application

Thesis | Full Stack Developer

React Native (For Mobile)

- React JS (For Website)
- Express JS (For Rest Api)

QR Code and SMS Gateway Attendance Application

MA Alkhairaat Pusat Palu | Full Stack Developer

- React Native (For Mobile)
- React JS (For Website)
- Express JS (For Rest Api)

- MySQL (For Database)
- React Redux
- Python

MySQL (For Database)

- React Redux
- **Twilio**

Palu City

Palu City

Des 2023 – Jan 2024

Agu 2024 - Sep 2024

MY SKILLS

- Hard Skill: JavaScript, React Native, Next JS, Express JS, and MySQL
- Soft Skill: Public Speaking, Problem Solving Skills, Able to adapt and work in a team.
- Software Skill: Microsoft Office